University of Connecticut 1998.0187
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series VI: Personal Files, undated, 1915-2005
  - Notebook - notes for travel book on India, Sudan, and Kenya, undated (Box 46)
  - Pittsburgh - notes, meeting agendas, clippings, from University of Pittsburgh, 1956-1960 (Box 47)
  - Graduate School of Public & International Affairs, UPitt - notes, programs, 1958-1959 (Box 47)
  - Graduate School of Public & International Affairs, UPitt - lectures, assignments, speeches, 1959 (Box 47)
  - Asian Geography, UPitt - lecture notes, 1957-1958 (Box 47)
  - Essentials of Public Administration, UPitt - lecture notes, course materials, 1959 (Box 47)
  - Comparative Civil Services - Graduate School of Public & International Affairs, UPitt - lecture notes, course materials, 1958 (Box 47)
  - Administrative Science Program - speeches, 1956 (Box 47)
  - Pakistan report, 1959 (Box 47)
  - McKinsey & Co. - reports, correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 47)
  - Peace Corps - notes, reports, correspondence during term as Peace Corps rep. in Thailand, 1961-1964 (Box 47)
  - VISTA - clippings, notes, reports, correspondence during term as director of VISTA, 1964-1966 (Box 47)
  - Kenya - notes, correspondence, ephemera during ambassadorship (Box 47)
    - 1966
    - 1967
    - 1968-1969
  - Long Island University - notes, clippings, ephemera during tenure as chancellor of LIU, undated (Box 47)
  - Kenya Outline - notes and clippings, 2002-2005 (Box 47)
  - Books by Glenn W. Ferguson (Box 47)
    - Unconventional Wisdom - Pendart Pro Books, 1999
    - Tilting at Religion - Prometheus Books, 2003
    - Sports in America - Sunstone Press, 2004
    - Traveling the Exotic - Sunstone Press, 2005
  - Administrative Science Quarterly, 1956 June (Box 47)